http://www.aspsys.com/privacy-policy/

Request a Quote
Welcome,
Search
()
Login to your Account
E-mail:
Password:
Request Password Reset Link
E-mail:
Cancel
Request
×Close
Register for an Account
First Name:
*
Last Name:
*
Phone:
*
Login (email address):
*
Company:
Password:
*
Password Confirm:
*
Address:
*
Address 2:
City:
*
Country:
*
United States
State:
*
State/Province:
Postal Code:
Request Email Confirmation Code
E-mail:
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy Statement establishes the privacy policy pertaining to the Aspen Systems website. By using the site, you are agreeing to the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy. For terms and conditions applying to use of the Aspen Systems website, please review our Terms of Use.
For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” means any information by which you can be personally identified, and includes but is not limited to your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address. Aspen Systems may request Personal Information in order to serve you better. Aspen Systems will collect Personal Information only when you voluntarily submit such Personal Information to us.
For each visitor to the site, our web server automatically records information regarding the visitor’s browser software, IP address, domain name (or that of the visitor’s access provider), e-mail address (if available) and other session identifying information. Regardless of the purpose for which it is submitted, it is Aspen Systems’s policy is to maintain all Personal Information as confidential, and to use such personal information only for the following purposes:
To fulfill your requests by us or by others involved in fulfillment
To improve the content, appearance and utility of the Aspen Systems website
To non-identifiably track visitors’ use of the Aspen Systems website for market research
To develop our business relationship with business partners or vendors
To identify and prevent spam, DDOS attacks, viruses, malware, or other electronic abuse which could potentially effect out stakeholders
Aspen Systems abides by the EU/US Safe Harbor Framework. To correct inaccuracies in our personal information, contact us at
webmaster@aspsys.com , or by phone at 1-800-992-9242.
Aspen Systems reserves the right, at its discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. You should check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of this site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy Statement will mean that you accept those changes.
Discover the Solution
At Aspen Systems we believe every complex problem has a simple solution. Our expert sales engineers will create a state of the art system, using the latest generation of technology, and provide world-class results.
Whether you need a simple server or a full turn-key solution, we’re here to help.
Learn more about the advantages of working with us, and our commitment to manufacturing excellence.
Contact us by filling out the form or call us toll-free at (800) 992-9242.
How did you hear about us?*
We respect your privacy. You're information will never be shared with a 3rd party.
©2020 Aspen Systems Inc. All Rights Reserved.
